Dreams are just a spark away!
Monster High: Electrified is a family, animation
film directed by Jun Falkenstein.
When Clawdeen dreams of opening a salon made for monsters and normies, Frankie
has the perfect place - an abandoned power station outside town.
But the idea sparks negative voltage when Moanica plots to ruin the whole
thing, and replace the celebration with something a little more...
Luckily the ghouls have a secret weapon on their side...Twyla, the daughter of
the Boogey Man, and the perfect ghoul to unearth any mystery.
Along with the most voltageous salon ever!
So catch every twist, turn, zap and blast...because the
Monster High ghouls are about to get ELECTRIC!
Draculaura (voice), played by Debi Derryberry.
Frankie / Venus (voice), played by Cassandra Lee Morris.
Clawdeen / Cleo (voice), played by Salli Saffioti.
Lagoona (voice), played by Larissa Gallagher.
Moanica / Woolee (voice), played by Cristina Milizia.
Twyla / Ari (voice), played by Jonquil Goode.
This article lists all the films and television specials based on Monster High, an
American fashion doll and media franchise launched by Mattel on June 11, 2010.
The films and television specials were broadcast on Nickelodeon in the United States and
released on home video formats by Universal Pictures Home Entertainment until 2017.
In 2016, Mattel rebooted the franchise with the release of an origin story film special titled Welcome to
Monster High, using updated animation modules and technologies, which released the following year.
On February 23, 2021, Mattel through its television division announced a second relaunch with an animated TV series and a live-action
musical film based on the franchise, which released on both Nickelodeon and Paramount+ in the United States in October 2022.
The tone is mind_bending.